Capital District Regional Planning Commission; Records apap380
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Greater Region, 1934-1997; 6; 6.43 cubic ft.
  - Mohawk Valley, Classifications and Standards of Quality and Purity Assigned to Fresh Surface Water Within the Mohawk River Drainage Basin …, 1954 May (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Mohawk Valley, EMS Federal Assistance Application 1203(1) Establishment and Initial Operation Emergency Medical Service System (1 of 2), 1980 March (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Mohawk Valley, EMS Federal Assistance Application 1203(1) Establishment and Initial Operation Emergency Medical Service System (2 of 2), 1980 March (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Mohawk Valley, General Aviation Study-Mohawk Valley Region, 1970 August (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Mohawk Valley, The Mohawk Regional Economic Study, Phase 1: Basic Inventory, 1968 August (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Mohawk Valley, Mohawk River Drainage Basin Survey Series Report No. 2, 1952 May (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Mohawk Valley, The Mohawk Valley: Business Infrastructure and Local Economic Development, 1991 May (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Mohawk Valley, Schoharie Creek Drainage Basin Comprehensive Plan for the Prevention and Abatement of Pollution, 1964 January (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Mohawk Valley, Summary of the Water Quality Management Plan for Mohawk River Planning Areas 12-01 and 12-03, 1976 October (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Mohawk Valley, Tomorrow's Jobs Tomorrow's Workers- Mohawk Valley Region, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Montgomery County, Comprehensive Public Water Supply Study CPWS-26, 1969 May (Oversized 1)
  - Montgomery County, Comprehensive Sewerage Study WPC-CS-178, 1970 January (Oversized 1)
  - Montgomery County, A Comprehensive Transportation Plan for Montgomery County, 1975 June (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Montgomery County, A Demographic Profile, 1990 June (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Montgomery County, Economic Study, 1973 October (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Montgomery County, Economic Profile, 1975 December-1976 March (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Montgomery County, Housing Needs, Resources and Support Capacity, 1974 May (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Montgomery County, Housing Plan: Recommendations for Implementation, 1975 May (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Montgomery County, Housing: Systems Housing and the Tax Impact, 1972 June (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Montgomery County, Land Use Analysis and plan, 1975 June (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Montgomery County, Memorandum: Community Facilities (Basis For Studies), 1975 June (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Montgomery County, Memorandum: HUD Area-Wide Planning Requirements, 1974 June (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Montgomery County, Okwari Park, Comprehensive Master Plan, 1973 February (Oversized 2)
  - Montgomery County, Open Space Plan, 1972 August (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Montgomery County, Overall Program Design Revised 1974, 1974 June (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Montgomery County, Planning and Development Phase 1, 1970 July (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Montgomery County, Population Study, 1973 October (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Montgomery County, Transportation Sketch Plan for Montgomery County, New York, 1974 August (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Montgomery County, Two Year Report July 1972-June 1974, 1974 June (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - NY-NJ Metro, Demographic Tends in the NY-NJ Metropolitan Region: 16-19 Year Old Age Group, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - NY-NJ Metro, Demographic Trends in the NY-NJ Metropolitan Region: Educational Attainment and Economic Opportunity, 1994 June (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - NY Metro, Demographic Trends in the NU-NJ Metropolitan Region: Income Distribution and Poverty, 1994 January (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - NY-NJ Metro, Regional Economy: Review 1993 Outlook 1994 for the New York-New Jersey Metropolitan Region, 1994 March (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - NY-NJ Metro, Regional Economy: Review 1994 Outlook 1995 for the New York-New Jersey Metropolitan Region, 1995 April (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - NY-NJ Metro, Demographic Tends in the NY-NJ Metropolitan Region: Racial and Ethnic Diversity, 1992 November (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - New York State, Community Profile 8: Upper Hudson Planning Region, 1969 July (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - New York State, Community Profile 9: Upper Mohawk Valley Planning Region, 1969 July (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - New York State, Community Profile 10: Lake Champlain/Lake George Planning Region, 1969 July (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - New York State, Community Profile 12: Mid-Hudson Planning Region, 1969 July (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - New York State, New York State Planning and Development Region, 1970 August (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - New York State, This New York State [1960s Informational Booklet], Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - New York State, A Progress Report to the National Resources Board on the Making of a State Plan for New York, March 1 to September 1, 1934 (Oversized 3)
  - Northeastern New York, An Assessment of the Effectiveness of the Northeast Industrial Waste Exchange During its First Six Months, 1987 January (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Northeastern New York, Finding Common Ground: The Draft Recommendations of the Northern Forest Lands Council, 1994 March (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Northeastern New York, Lake Champlain/Lake George Regional Recreation Study, 1970 March (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Northeastern New York, Northeast Industrial Waste Exchange Listings Catalog, Issue No. 13, 1984 August (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Northeastern New York, A Profile of Need: A Study of Post-Secondary Education Needs in Northeastern New York State, 1974 December (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Northeastern New York, A Study of Land Use Regulations and Controls for the Lake Champlain-Lake George Region, Undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Northeast New York, Water Resources of Champlain-Upper Hudson Basins in New York State, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Schoharie County, Economic Profile, 1976 March-1976 June (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Schoharie County, Housing Analysis, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - [Town of] Summit, Comprehensive Master Plan, 1986 June (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - [Village of] Tarrytown, Local Waterfront Revitalization Plan Document [Draft] (1 of 2), 1989 September (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - [Village of] Tarrytown, Local Waterfront Revitalization Plan Document [Draft] (2 of 2), 1989 September (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Upstate NY, Groundwater Supply Source Protection-A Guide for Localities in Upstate New York, 1984 December (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Western New York, Technical Report on Housing in Erie-Niagara Region-First Year Study, 1970 June (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Western New York, Trucking Needs Study, 1983 August (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - [Town of] Wright, Subdivision Regulations, 1989 August (Box 6, Folder 41)